Things sure have changed. Not everyone
believes it, but the bad guys went good.
And we cannot wait for society to
welcome us with open arms. Aren't you a
notorious criminal? Yes. No. Maybe.
Sorry. Sorry. Nerves. It hasn't been
easy with a reputation like ours. You
want to work at a bank? Why not? Some of
my best memories are at banks. You
robbed us three times. Duh. That was
this bank.
How are we supposed to get a fresh start
if no one will trust us? I'm keeping my
eye on you guys. What? What was that? I
panicked. Okay, I'm a panicer.
The name's Kitty and these are my
associates. So, you're like the bad
girl. We need the bad guys for the
biggest heist in history. Maybe you
don't keep up with the news, but we're
good now. I'm not exactly asking.
Don't tell me you guys are bad again.
No, we're being set up. We need to show
the world we're good. So, we're going to
sabotage him.
All right, Mr. Master of Disguise,
you're up. I promise to play you
respectfully. My
flowers, do your thing. I'll be your
hacker today. Snake, we're going to need
some extra muscle. I'm late for a
venyasa. Venyasa. You think I got this
body by sitting around watching TV? And
then we just have to tear them apart
limb by limb until all they can remember
is pain.
Wow. Okay. I was going to say stop him,
but sure. If there's time, we can do the
limb thing.
First time for everything, right?
Pull us up, snake
vignasa,
baby. Come on.
Are you kidding me? Lefty loosey, righty
tighty.
Oh, right.
You're not nervous, right? Cuz we know
what happens when you're nervous, buddy.
I'm sorry. What? No. No. No.
No. Help me. Stay with me, B. Stay with
me.
Racing is my dream.
I could race in the Grand Prix and I
could win. You'll get your chance to
race someday. He is the fourtime Grand
Prix champion.
It's Ed's car.
This is unhealthy.
Stop. Get out of my car. Okay. And
[Applause]
your arms like a noodle. I'm over here.
There's your arm.
It's not broken. No driving for a few
weeks. Weeks. I have an idea. We look
alike. I could take your place. Also,
you give me half the prize money or
there's no deal. All right, deal. I
can't believe I'm going to drive in the
Grand Prix.
Neither can I.
Welcome to the Grand Prix. I must be
dreaming.
Nice driving.
Be careful. One mistake can cost you.
That was totally a threat. I still
really want his autograph, though.
He's completely lost control.
Maybe my dream should have stayed a
dream. I believe in you, Ed. You've got
this.
Watch this. This is unbelievable.
[Music]
Wa. Yeah. Wa.
Are you ready to get pumped up?
Hello everyone. I have big news. I found
Smurf Village. I'm one step closer to
total evil
dominance. Lame. You're all lame.
Hit it, papa.
[Music]
I
think
it feel like a friend.
What the smurf?
No, I think I just smurfed my pants.
Code blue
from Paramount Pictures. We got to
rescue Papa. Let me guess. Papa Smurf's
in trouble.
We are storming Rosamel's castle and we
take no prisoners except for Papa. We'll
make sure and grab him. Everybody know
the game to do. We're going to need help
from
the Snood Poots. Snutder Poots.
Hey, what are they saying?
this July. If we don't stop these
wizards,
it'll mean the end of the universe.
Sound effect. Smurf, can you back off?
Let's go smurf that wizard up. Oh, yeah.
Get ready. Race for impact for an
adventure that will blow you away. Come
on.
What the Smurf?
Hold on, you little Smurf.
We're here to save everything. Goodbye,
Smurfves. Forever.
Now that's what I call a banger. Smurfs
featuring new music by Rihanna and more.
It's a new day. We're taking a trip to
spend the week with my grandma.
Buckle up, Gabby Catch. It's time to go.
Here we go.
Do you want to come to San Francisco
with us? Let's do it.
We're here.
The
dollhouse. Not over dramatic. I think
we're moving.
Everyone clean left. The other left.
Baby box. I'm learning so much today.
Molina. Mommy will be right back. Who is
that?
What do we have here? Vera wondered
aloud as a man in the street yelled at
her. Seriously, lady, what is wrong with
you?
This dollhouse will complete my cat
collection. Add to cart. No, girl. Bye.
It's time to get tiny. Let's get this
dollhouse back. We're leaving the
planet. Oh, this is awesome. You can
come.
My hair, my tushy, my fashion. Oh, wait.
Can I scratch that? I look fabulous.
[Music]
I have a feeling we're going to need
backup. What's wrong? This is a
dollhouse problem.
Oops. Looks like cakey got faked.
Here we go. Marina, bring me my yoga
mat.
Oh, pulling out the wishbone. You are
really trying to destroy the universe
right now, aren't
[Music]
you? Help.
Toothless. It's okay. I won't hurt you.
Everything we know about
dragons is wrong.
The reign of the dragons. It's right
here, right now.
I'm the first Viking
who wouldn't kill a dragon. First to
ride one, though.
All right, bud. You ready?
[Applause]
[Music]
Come on. Come on. Yeah. Look at
us. My fault.
You have something none of us
Come on, bud.
[Music]
Watch out.
Hey, Magic Mirror. Who's the fairest of
them all? Why, Shrek, of course.
Ew, Dad. Woohoo! Mama light. Who's
making this stuff? Not me.
Whoa.
Shrek 5 starring Mike Myers, Eddie
Murphy, Cameron Diaz, and Zandea. Oh,
damn. Only in theaters Christmas 2026.